Contact

225 Garðabær, Iceland (+354) 866-1321 (Mobile) jonnxor@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jonnxor (LinkedIn) www.jonnxor.is/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Next.js React.js TypeScript

Languages

Icelandic (Native or Bilingual)
English (Professional Working)

Jón Agnar Stefánsson

Senior Frontend Web Developer Iceland

Summary

Senior Web Developer with 10 years of experience in popular web technologies and methodologies.

I have worked on multiple large projects across various web frameworks, with a strong focus on project architecture, maintainability, readability, performance optimizations, and strict adherence to best practices.

I describe myself as a man of principle who likes to take life one day at a time, continuously seeking out new challenges and opportunities to improve my skills, knowledge, and understanding.

Additionally, my other interests include art, culture, language, history, mythology, philosophy, and more.

Experience

Advania Ísland Web Developer May 2016 - April 2024 (8 years) Reykjavík, Iceland

Reykjavik University
Teaching Assistant
2016 - 2016 (less than a year)
Reykjavík, Iceland

Skeljungur Attendant 2015 - 2015 (less than a year) Reykjavík, Capital Region, Iceland

Outcome Technician

2012 - 2014 (2 years)

Reykjavík, Iceland

Education

Reykjavik University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2013 - 2016)

Technical College of Iceland

Associate's degree, Computer Science · (2009 - 2013)